Litchfield County judicial records
Litchfield Historical Society
Litchfield County judicial records
1790-1930
1790-1861
Litchfield Historical Society 7 South Street, P.O. Box 385 Litchfield, CT, 6759 URL: http://www.litchfieldhistoricalsociety.org/archon Email: archivist@litchfieldhistoricalsociety.org Phone: 860-567-4501 Fax: 860-567-3565
2.50
Litchfield County Judicial Records (1790-1930) consist of case files and other documents relating to matters involving the Litchfield County Court, the Litchfield Superior Court, and the clerk of the court from the late 1790s through 1861. The records were recovered from the attic of the former Westleigh Inn and it is not known why the records were stored there. They appear to complement the Litchfield County Court records held by the Connecticut State Archives. In the absence of original order, they have been arranged in two series, Case files and Subject files, using two State Archives finding aids as models: "RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Files, Inventory of Records" and "RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Papers by Subject Inventory of Records," both of which were prepared by Debra Pond. The description of the series and records which follow include excerpts from these State Archives finding aids.
2005-08-0
Scope and Contents
Litchfield County Judicial Records (1790-1930) consist of case files and other documents relating to matters involving the Litchfield County Court, the Litchfield Superior Court, and the clerk of the court from the late 1790s through 1861. The records were recovered from the attic of the former Westleigh Inn and it is not known why the records were stored there. They appear to complement the Litchfield County Court records held by the Connecticut State Archives. In the absence of original order, they have been arranged in two series, Case files and Subject files, using two State Archives finding aids as models: "RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Files, Inventory of Records" and "RG 003, Litchfield County, County Court Papers by Subject Inventory of Records," both of which were prepared by Debra Pond. The description of the series and records which follow include excerpts from these State Archives finding aids.
Series 1, Case files, contain original materials and relate to civil lawsuits and criminal actions in the years between 1790 and 1861. While the records relating to each file vary by case, common documents include writs, summonses, motions filed by the parties, and jury verdicts. The cases are arranged chronologically and then alphabetically by plaintiff.
Series 2, Subject files, include a range of records and generally follow the subject categories found in the Litchfield County Court records at the Connecticut State Archives. The categories are organized alphabetically, and then arranged chronologically within each category.
Subject file categories:
Admissions to the bar (1859-1860) contains chronologically arranged certificates from the county bar's committee of examiners reporting results of its examination of candidates seeking to be admitted to practice before the Litchfield County bar.
Appeals from probate (1800-1855) contains chronologically arranged documents from parties requesting reconsideration of probate court decisions.
Appointments of commissioners (1855-1860) contains chronologically arranged documents relating to confirmations of individuals sworn as commissioners of the court.
Costs (1798-1860, undated) are accountings of court costs from individual files for items such as service of writs, summoning of witnesses, juror expenses, sheriff's travel expenses and the like. Some cost records do not include the name of the case to which they belong. The records are filed chronologically by year.
Court expenses (1798-1859) are arranged chronologically and consist primarily of accounts by those incurring expenses in running the court. Entries include such items as dinner and wine expenses and some itemized gaoler accounts, which provide details of the care provided to prisoners while incarcerated in Litchfield.
Inquests (1798-1861) are investigations into the causes of suspicious deaths. They are arranged chronologically by year.
Jurors (circa 1800-1860) contains orders to town constables to summon jurors for jury duty, as the court needed them to try cases. In addition, the clerk's notes of the individuals who served on the jury for certain trials may be found here. These records are arranged first by general records, which include documents relating to county-wide matters, and second alphabetically by town name, then chronologically.
Justices by town (1860-1861) contains documents confirming the swearing of justices of the peace and are arranged alphabetically by town.
Miscellaneous (1802-circa 1930) contains a variety of material and generally consists of individual items. Documents include a land appraisal, a bond, a deposition apparently unrelated to any case file, documents relating to post-Civil War military pensions, photographs of two unidentified men circa 1930, and other items.
Naturalization (1842-1860) is made up of petitions for and other documents relating to naturalization. They are arranged chronologically and then by the name of the individual.
Protection Orders (1799-1812) protected debtors with a large number of debts from arrest while at court suing their own creditors. They are arranged chronologically.
Taverns (1856-1860) is composed of chronologically arranged certifications to the court of the tavern keepers appointed by the county's towns. Tavern licenses were appointed, or renewed, annually by the court.
Arrangement of Materials
The records are arranged in two series:
Series 1. Case files
Series 2. Subject files
Related Materials
Connecticut State Archives, RG 003 Judicial Department:
Litchfield County, County Court Files, 1751-1855
Litchfield County, County Court Papers by Subject, 1750-1855
Litchfield County Court Minorities Collection, 1753-1854
Information about related materials is available at http://www.cslib.org/archives/FAIndexes/
Index Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Genre/Form of Material:
Civil court records; Criminal court records; Judicial records
Topical Term:
Connecticut. County Court (Litchfield County) -- History; County courts -- Connecticut -- Litchfield County -- History
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Acquisition Information
The materials were acquired by Litchfield Historical Society from Albert DiMeo on 08/03/2005.
Accruals
Albert DiMeo made an initial gift on Aug. 3, 2005 (2005-08-0). Mr. DiMeo through his daughter Laurel Saramak made a smaller additional donation on Apr. 25, 2007 (2007-14-0).
Other Information
This collection was processed with support from the Council on Library and Information Resources (CLIR) and the National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC).
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Case files
  Arranged by the latest year of the court term if known; otherwise, by latest date as indicated in the documents.
  - Fleming v. Lord, 1790 (Folder 1)
  - Fleming v. Lord, 1790 (Folder 2)
  - State v. Dony, 1792 (Folder 3)
  - Henshaw et. al. v. Austin, 1798 (Folder 4)
  - Henshaw v. Marsh, 1798 (Folder 5)
  - Simons v. Simons, 1798 (Folder 6)
  - State v. Shelton, 1798 (Folder 7)
  - Swift v. Doty, 1798 (Folder 8)
  - Vantuyl v. Thrall et al., 1798 (Folder 9)
  - Webster v. Bacon, 1798 (Folder 10)
  - Buell v. Swift et al., 1799 (Folder 11)
  - Reed v. Cook., 1799 (Folder 12)
  - State v. Mott, 1799 (Folder 13)
  - State v. Robinson, 1799 (Folder 14)
  - Fairchild v. Beckley, 1800 (Folder 15)
  - State v. Morey, 1800 (Folder 16)
  - Fulford v. Doty et al., 1801 (Folder 17)
  - Judson v. Steele, 1801 (Folder 18)
  - Waterman v. Chapin, 1801 (Folder 19)
  - Waterman v. Scofield, 1801 (Folder 20)
  - Case et al. v. Phelps, 1802 (Folder 21)
  - Hale v. Hale, 1802 (Folder 22)
  - Hodges v. Yale, 1802 (Folder 23)
  - Hogaboom v. Hosmer, 1802 (Folder 24)
  - Merils v. Collier, 1802 (Folder 25)
  - Perkins v. Cutler and Smith, 1802 (Folder 26)
  - State v. Adams, 1802 (Folder 27)
  - State v. Heath, 1802 (Folder 28)
  - Taylor v. Deming, 1802 (Folder 29)
  - Bunel v. Blakeslee, 1803 (Folder 30)
  - Warner v. Warner, 1803 (Folder 31)
  - Phelps v. Becker, 1804 (Folder 32)
  - Ruggles v. Parsons, 1804 (Folder 33)
  - State v. Blakeslee, 1804 (Folder 34)
  - Phelps v. Landon, 1805 (Folder 35)
  - Morgan v. State, 1806 (Folder 36)
  - Sawyer v. Mitchelson, 1807 (Folder 37)
  - Seymour v. Lee, 1807 (Folder 38)
  - Sheldon v. Rockwell, 1807 (Folder 39)
  - Ely v. Norton, 1808 (Folder 40)
  - Lewis v. Collier, 1808 (Folder 41)
  - Lewis v. Norton, 1808 (Folder 42)
  - Plumb v. Baldwin, 1808 (Folder 43)
  - State v. Harger, 1808 (Folder 44)
  - Berry v. Fuller, 1810 (Folder 45)
  - Fletcher v. Devotion, 1810 (Folder 46)
  - Nettleton, petition, 1810 (Folder 47)
  - State v. Benson, 1811 (Folder 48)
  - Holly, petition, 1812 (Folder 49)
  - Gray v. Peck, 1814 (Folder 50)
  - Fanning et al. v. Bulkeley, 1834 (Folder 51)
  - Cooney v. Cooney, 1835 (Folder 52)
  - Sterling v. Pratt, 1837 (Folder 53)
  - Heacock et al. v. Leavitt et al., 1838 (Folder 54)
  - Knapp v. McMahon, 1838 (Folder 55)
  - Landon et al. v. Plymouth Congregational Society, 1838 (Folder 56)
  - Reynolds v. Newton, 1838 (Folder 57)
  - Stevens v. Sturges et al., 1838 (Folder 58)
  - Chamberlain v. Sedgewick et al., 1839 (Folder 59)
  - Lyman et al. v. Collins et al., 1839 (Folder 60)
  - North v. Allyn, 1839 (Folder 61)
  - Phoenix Bank v. Wolcott, 1839 (Folder 62)
  - Smedley v. Cowles, 1839 (Folder 63)
  - Webster v. Hungerford, Kellogg and Wilson, 1839 (Folder 64)
  - Wolcott v. Seeley, 1839 (Folder 65)
  - Fenn v. Camp, 1840 (Folder 66)
  - Roberts v. Johnson, 1840 (Folder 67)
  - Roberts v. Town of Barkhamsted, 1840 (Folder 68)
  - Rockwell v. French et al., 1840 (Folder 69)
  - Smith v. Fenn, 1840 (Folder 70)
  - Vincent et al. v. Camp, 1840 (Folder 71)
  - Watson et al. v. Gillett, 1840 (Folder 72)
  - Wilson v. Welles, 1840 (Folder 73)
  - Preston v. Dodge, 1841 (Folder 74)
  - Rellier v. Kellogg et al., 1841 (Folder 75)
  - Sage v. Lincoln, 1841 (Folder 76)
  - Reed et al. v. Sharon Manufacturing Co., 1842 (Folder 77)
  - New Milford and Litchfield Turnpike Co., petition, 1843 (Folder 78)
  - Porter v. Cooper, 1843 (Folder 79)
  - Reed v. Benson and Fuller, 1843 (Folder 80)
  - Steele v. Carrier, 1844 (Folder 81)
  - Webster v. Moss, 1844 (Folder 82)
  - Whetmore v. The Green Woods Turnpike Co., 1845 (Folder 83)
  - Freeman et al. v. Granger, 1847 (Folder 84)
  - Shilton v. Upson, 1847 (Folder 85)
  - Thornton v. Bradley, 1847 (Folder 86)
  - Dauchy v. Poineer, 1850 (Folder 87)
  - Stevens v. May, 1850 (Folder 88)
  - Woodworth v. Dutchess County Iron Co., 1850 (Folder 89)
  - Copeland v. Peters, 1851 (Folder 90)
  - Currier v. Ames, 1851 (Folder 91)
  - Easland v. Patterson, 1851 (Folder 92)
  - Graves v. Hamm, 1851 (Folder 93)
  - Judd v. Hurlburt, 1851 (Folder 94)
  - Munson v. Wickwire, 1851 (Folder 95)
  - Phillips v. Scoville, 1851 (Folder 96)
  - Scovill v. Riggs, 1851 (Folder 97)
  - Alfred v. Jones, 1852 (Folder 98)
  - Beckley v. Beckley, 1852 (Folder 99)
  - Bradley v. Hosford, 1852 (Folder 100)
  - Brown v. Moss, 1852 (Folder 101)
  - Burritt v. Wordin, 1852 (Folder 102)
  - Calkins v. Phillipps, 1852 (Folder 103)
  - Dean v. Wickwire, 1852 (Folder 104)
  - Dorsey v. Mason, 1852 (Folder 105)
  - Douglas v. Beckley, 1852 (Folder 106)
  - Ford v. Brown, 1852 (Folder 107)
  - Graves v. Miles at al., 1852 (Folder 108)
  - Gridley v. Goodwin, 1852 (Folder 109)
  - Hawley v. Bull, 1852 (Folder 110)
  - Johnson v. Town of Norfolk, 1852 (Folder 111)
  - Marsh v. Merchant, 1852 (Folder 112)
  - Marsh v. Northrop, 1852 (Folder 113)
  - McNeil v. Scoville, 1852 (Folder 114)
  - Merchant v. Merchant, 1852 (Folder 115)
  - Mills v. Hanly, 1852 (Folder 116)
  - Munson v. Beckley et al., 1852 (Folder 117)
  - Palmer et al. v. Parmely, 1852 (Folder 118)
  - Pond v. Hine, 1852 (Folder 119)
  - Sperry and Tomlinson v. Tomlinson, 1852 (Folder 120)
  - Stone v. Wadhams et al., 1852 (Folder 121)
  - Andrews v. Wilcox, 1853 (Folder 122)
  - Babbitt v. Beardsley, 1853 (Folder 123)
  - Cornwall Iron Co. v. Wheaton, 1853 (Folder 124)
  - Fox v. Hayes et al., 1853 (Folder 125)
  - Hawley v. Miles, 1853 (Folder 126)
  - Hopson v. Johnson, 1853 (Folder 127)
  - Howland v. Hill, 1853 (Folder 128)
  - Lee v. Camp, 1853 (Folder 129)
  - Leonard v. Sherwood, 1853 (Folder 130)
  - Merrill v. Town of Simsbury, 1853 (Folder 131)
  - Richards v. Jewett, 1853 (Folder 132)
  - Sanford v. Graves, 1853 (Folder 133)
  - Sanford v. Mead, 1853 (Folder 134)
  - State v. Butler, 1853 (Folder 135)
  - Terry v. Hamm, 1853 (Folder 136)
  - Welch v. Landon, 1853 (Folder 137)
  - Andrus v. Kelley, 1854 (Folder 138)
  - Bacon v. Bacon, 1854 (Folder 139)
  - Barton v. Harris, 1854 (Folder 140)
  - Best v. Niven, 1854 (Folder 141)
  - Bradley v. Richmond, 1854 (Folder 142)
  - Buck v. Connecticut Silva Steel Co., 1854 (Folder 143)
  - Gillick v. Farrell, 1854 (Folder 144)
  - Hartford, Providence and Fishkill R. R. Co. v. Brown et al., 1854 (Folder 145)
  - Hartford, Providence and Fishkill R. R. Co. v. Sturgess, 1854 (Folder 146)
  - Sherwood v. Ferris, 1854 (Folder 147)
  - Smith v. Carrington, 1854 (Folder 148)
  - Stearns v. Hill et al., 1854 (Folder 149)
  - Uriah Waterbury v. Housatonic Rail Road Co., 1854 (Folder 150)
  - Wolcottville Knitting Co. v. Shipley, 1854 (Folder 151)
  - Ansonia Brass and Battery Co. v. American Percussion Cap Co., 1855 (Folder 152)
  - Atwood v. Hotchkiss, 1855 (Folder 153)
  - Beach v. The Tanning Co., 1855 (Folder 154)
  - Bennett and Stark v. McAuley, 1855 (Folder 155)
  - Berkshire Woolen Co. v. Union Woolen Co., 1855 (Folder 156)
  - Booth v. Booth, 1855 (Folder 157)
  - Burwell v. Hart et al., 1855 (Folder 158)
  - Clifton Lumber Co. v. Eads, 1855 (Folder 159)
  - Dayton v. Smith, 1855 (Folder 160)
  - Dean v. Town of Bristol, 1855 (Folder 161)
  - Gardner v. Gardner, 1855 (Folder 162)
  - George Hill Co. v. Salisbury Iron Co., 1855 (Folder 163)
  - Graves v. Page et al., 1855 (Folder 164)
  - Henderson v. Green, 1855 (Folder 165)
  - Henderson v. Hoyt, 1855 (Folder 166)
  - Hubbard and Stedman v. Hodge and Co., 1855 (Folder 167)
  - Hungerford v. Case, 1855 (Folder 168)
  - Johnson et al. v. Johnson, 1855 (Folder 169)
  - Lyman v. Morgan et al., 1855 (Folder 170)
  - Merwin v. Cable, 1855 (Folder 171)
  - Mitchell, petition, 1855 (Folder 172)
  - Mitchell v. Ward et al., 1855 (Folder 173)
  - Morehouse v. Beebe, 1855 (Folder 174)
  - Northfield Manufacturing Co. v. Renfield, 1855 (Folder 175)
  - Parsons v. Bronson, 1855 (Folder 176)
  - Sallspaugh v. Sallspaugh, 1855 (Folder 177)
  - Simon v. Videto, 1855 (Folder 178)
  - Smith v. Cushman, 1855 (Folder 179)
  - Smith v. Hatch, 1855 (Folder 180)
  - Smith v. McGraw, 1855 (Folder 181)
  - Todd v. Richardson, 1855 (Folder 182)
  - Treadwell v. Cushman, 1855 (Folder 183)
  - Whiting v. Welton, 1855 (Folder 184)
  - Wilson v. Scott, 1855 (Folder 185)
  - Woodward and Co. v. Barnes, 1855 (Folder 186)
  - State v. Donnelly, 1856 (Folder 187)
  - Foot v. Chatfield, 1858 (Folder 188)
  - Graham v. Thomas, 1858 (Folder 189)
  - Spencer v. Howe and Wetmore, 1858 (Folder 190)
  - State v. Beach, 1858 (Folder 191)
  - State v. Just, 1858 (Folder 192)
  - State v. Williams, 1858 (Folder 193)
  - Trowbridge v. Trowbridge, 1858 (Folder 194)
  - Cothren et al. Bradley et al., 1859 (Folder 195)
  - Kellogg v. Ripley, 1859 (Folder 196)
  - Squires v. Town of Sharon, 1859 (Folder 197)
  - State v. Beckwith, 1859 (Folder 198)
  - State v. Bradley, 1859 (Folder 199)
  - State v. Carley, 1859 (Folder 200)
  - State v. Cogswell et al., 1859 (Folder 201)
  - State v. Deming, 1859 (Folder 202)
  - State v. Griswold, 1859 (Folder 203)
  - State v. Kelly, 1859 (Folder 204)
  - State v. Morey et al., 1859 (Folder 205)
  - State v. Palmeter, 1859 (Folder 206)
  - State v. Ryan, 1859 (Folder 207)
  - State v. Shinnis, 1859 (Folder 208)
  - State v. Thayer, 1859 (Folder 209)
  - State v. Thomas, 1859 (Folder 210)
  - State v. Webster, 1859 (Folder 211)
  - State v. Young, 1859 (Folder 212)
  - Wilcox v. Bradford, 1859 (Folder 213)
  - Bacon v. Richards, 1860 (Folder 214)
  - Bennett v. Whittlesey, 1860 (Folder 215)
  - Buckingham v. Buckingham, 1860 (Folder 216)
  - Hatch v. Cogswell, 1860 (Folder 217)
  - Hine v. Hine, 1860 (Folder 218)
  - Humphrey v. Miner et al., 1860 (Folder 219)
  - Munson v. Munson et al., 1860 (Folder 220)
  - Oram v. Wadhams Manufacturing Co., 1860 (Folder 221)
  - Phelps v. Bradford, 1860 (Folder 222)
  - Root v. Manchester, 1860 (Folder 223)
  - State v. Corcoran, 1860 (Folder 224)
  - State v. Dayton et al., 1860 (Folder 225)
  - State v. Hazelton, 1860 (Folder 226)
  - State v. Pusey, 1860 (Folder 227)
  - State v. Vanalstyne, 1860 (Folder 228)
  - Studley v. Peck, 1860 (Folder 229)
  - Whittlesey v. Smith et al., 1860 (Folder 230)
  - Rodgers v. Pratt, 1861 (Folder 231)
  - Everts v. Chittenden, undated (Folder 232)
  - State v. Breston, undated (Folder 233)
  - Tyler v. Dunbar, undated (Folder 234)
  - Wheeler v. Munson, undated (Folder 235)
- Subject files
  Arranged alphabetically by category and then chronologically.
  - Admissions to the bar, 1859-1861 (Folder 1)
  - Appeals from probate, Prentice, John, 1800 (Folder 2)
  - Appeals from probate, Townshend, Jacob, 1800 (Folder 3)
  - Appeals from probate, Loomis, Joseph, 1807 (Folder 4)
  - Appeals from probate, Bryant, Charles and Bryant, Luther, 1852 (Folder 5)
  - Appeals from probate, Johnson, Mary, 1855 (Folder 6)
  - Appointments of commissioners, 1855-1860 (Folder 7)
  - Costs, 1798 (Folder 8)
  - Costs, 1799 (Folder 9)
  - Costs, 1800-1811 (Folder 10)
  - Costs, 1839-1849 (Folder 11)
  - Costs, 1851-1858 (Folder 12)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 13)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 14)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 15)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 16)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 17)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 18)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 19)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 20)
  - Costs, 1859 (Folder 21)
  - Costs, 1860 (Folder 22)
  - Costs, 1860 (Folder 23)
  - Costs, 1860 (Folder 24)
  - Costs, undated (Folder 25)
  - Court expenses, 1799-1800 (Folder 26)
  - Court expenses, 1803, 1806 (Folder 27)
  - Court expenses, 1808-1816 (Folder 28)
  - Court expenses, 1839-1859 (Folder 29)
  - Inquests, Smith, Theophilus, 1798 (Folder 30)
  - Inquests, Tuttle, Charles, 1800 (Folder 31)
  - Inquests, Bostford, Merab, 1801 (Folder 32)
  - Inquests, Morgan, Samuel, 1801 (Folder 33)
  - Inquests, Richardson, Abigail, 1803 (Folder 34)
  - Inquests, Yorker, John alias Whitford, John, 1803 (Folder 35)
  - Inquests, Dormady, Thomas, 1804 (Folder 36)
  - Inquests, Morris, Richard, 1806 (Folder 37)
  - Inquests, Hart, Stephen, 1807 (Folder 38)
  - Inquests, unknown "black woman", 1811 (Folder 39)
  - Inquests, Stewart, William, 1812 (Folder 40)
  - Inquests, Brown, John, 1856 (Folder 41)
  - Inquests, Bartholomew, John, 1859 (Folder 42)
  - Inquests, Lewis, John, 1859 (Folder 43)
  - Inquests, Rood, Rufus, 1859 (Folder 44)
  - Inquests, Booth, Sidney, 1860 (Folder 45)
  - Inquests, Coffee, Edwin, 1860 (Folder 46)
  - Inquests, Fitzgibbons, Patrick, 1860 (Folder 47)
  - Inquests, Vitteloe, Lucy, 1860 (Folder 48)
  - Inquests, Vitteloe, Phoebe, 1860 (Folder 49)
  - Inquests, Murphy, Isaac, 1861 (Folder 50)
  - Jurors, general, circa 1800 (Folder 51)
  - Jurors, general, circa 1800 (Folder 52)
  - Jurors, general, 1801 (Folder 53)
  - Jurors, general, 1807 Feb (Folder 54)
  - Jurors, general, 1807 Aug (Folder 55)
  - Jurors, general, 1808 Feb (Folder 56)
  - Jurors, general, 1808 Aug (Folder 57)
  - Jurors, general, 1809 Feb (Folder 58)
  - Jurors, general, 1810 Feb (Folder 59)
  - Jurors, general, 1810 Aug (Folder 60)
  - Jurors, general, 1811 Feb (Folder 61)
  - Jurors, general, 1811 Aug (Folder 62)
  - Jurors, general, 1812 Feb (Folder 63)
  - Jurors, general, 1812 Aug (Folder 64)
  - Jurors, general, 1850-1860, undated (Folder 65)
  - Jurors, Barkhamsted, 1803-1860 (Folder 66)
  - Jurors, Bethlehem, 1859-1860 (Folder 67)
  - Jurors, Bridgewater, 1860 (Folder 68)
  - Jurors, Canaan, 1798, 1860 (Folder 69)
  - Jurors, Colebrook, 1860 (Folder 70)
  - Jurors, Cornall, 1805-1809 (Folder 71)
  - Jurors, Cornwall, 1810, 1815 (Folder 72)
  - Jurors, Cornwall, 1858-1860 (Folder 73)
  - Jurors, Goshen, 1805, 1807 (Folder 74)
  - Jurors, Goshen, 1808-1811 (Folder 75)
  - Jurors, Goshen, 1856-1860 (Folder 76)
  - Jurors, Harwinton, 1856-1860 (Folder 77)
  - Jurors, Kent, 1810-1859 (Folder 78)
  - Jurors, Litchfield, 1798-1810 (Folder 79)
  - Jurors, Litchfield, 1856-1860 (Folder 80)
  - Jurors, New Hartford, 1856, 1859 (Folder 81)
  - Jurors, New Milford, 1856 (Folder 82)
  - Jurors, Norfolk, 1856 (Folder 83)
  - Jurors, North Canaan, 1860 (Folder 84)
  - Jurors, Plymouth, 1856, 1860 (Folder 85)
  - Jurors, Roxbury, 1856, 1860 (Folder 86)
  - Jurors, Salisbury, 1801-1808 (Folder 87)
  - Jurors, Salisbury, 1809-1812 (Folder 88)
  - Jurors, Salisbury, 1856-1860 (Folder 89)
  - Jurors, Sharon, 1800-1804 (Folder 90)
  - Jurors, Sharon, 1806-1812 (Folder 91)
  - Jurors, Sharon, 1856-1860 (Folder 92)
  - Jurors, Torrington, 1856-1860 (Folder 93)
  - Jurors, Warren, 1815-1860 (Folder 94)
  - Jurors, Washington, 1856-1860 (Folder 95)
  - Jurors, Watertown, 1799 (Folder 96)
  - Jurors, Watertown, 1859-1860 (Folder 97)
  - Jurors, Winchester, 1856, 1860 (Folder 98)
  - Jurors, Woodbury, 1859-1860 (Folder 99)
  - Justices by town, Barkhamsted, Bethlehem, Bridgewater, 1860 (Folder 100)
  - Justices by town, Canaan, Colebrook, Cornwall, 1860-1861 (Folder 101)
  - Justices by town, Goshen, Harwinton, 1860 (Folder 102)
  - Justices by town, Litchfield, 1860 (Folder 103)
  - Justices by town, Morris, New Hartford, New Milford, Norfolk, North Canaan, 1860 (Folder 104)
  - Justices by town, Plymouth, Salisbury, Sharon, Torrington, 1860-1861 (Folder 105)
  - Justices by town, Warren, 1860 (Folder 106)
  - Justices by town, Washington, Winchester, Woodbury, 1860 (Folder 107)
  - Miscellaneous, appraisement of land, Humphrey, Mary, 1802 (Folder 108)
  - Miscellaneous, bar meeting, 1860 (Folder 109)
  - Miscellaneous, bond, Fuller, Rufus and Fuller, Alphus, 1855 (Folder 110)
  - Miscellaneous, citation for Vanderpool, Henry and his wife and Sterling, E., 1807 (Folder 111)
  - Miscellaneous, certificate, justice of the peace Gorey, Augustus, 1860 (Folder 112)
  - Miscellaneous, correspondence, 1860, 1865 (Folder 113)
  - Miscellaneous, deposition re: Pixley and Phelps, Barkhamsted, circa 1795 (Folder 114)
  - Miscellaneous, military pension documents, 1882-1911 (Folder 115)
  - Miscellaneous, order of distribution, Meigs, John, 1795 (Folder 116)
  - Miscellaneous, photographs, circa 1930 (Folder 117)
  - Miscellaneous, probate court, Garnsey, Mary Ann, 1847 (Folder 118)
  - Miscellaneous, promissory notes, 1796, 1805 (Folder 119)
  - Miscellaneous, receipts for vol. 27 etc. Conn. Reports, 1860 (Folder 120)
  - Miscellaneous, resignation as deputy sheriff, Rockefeller, Philip, 1860 (Folder 121)
  - Miscelleanous, other papers, circa 1799-1859, undated (Folder 122)
  - Naturalization, 1842-1844 (Folder 123)
  - Naturalization, 1845-1846 (Folder 124)
  - Naturalization, 1850 (Folder 125)
  - Naturalization, 1851 (Folder 126)
  - Naturalization, B-H, 1852 (Folder 127)
  - Naturalization, L-W, 1852 (Folder 128)
  - Naturalization, 1854 (Folder 129)
  - Naturalization, 1855-1856 (Folder 130)
  - Naturalization, 1857 (Folder 131)
  - Naturalization, 1859-1860 (Folder 132)
  - Protection orders, 1799-1812 (Folder 133)
  - Taverns, Barkhamsted, Kent, Litchfield, 1856-1860 (Folder 134)
  - Taverns, Morris, New Milford, 1856-1860 (Folder 135)